<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sirat-al-Mustaqim</string>

    <string-array name="surah_names">
        <item>1. Al-Fatihah</item>
        <item>2. Al-Baqarah</item>
        <item>3. Al-Imran</item>
        <item>4. An-Nisa</item>
        <item>5. Al-Ma`idah</item>
        <item>6. Al-An`am</item>
        <item>7. Al-A`raf</item>
        <item>8. Al-Anfal</item>
        <item>9. At-Tawbah</item>
        <item>10. Yunus</item>
        <item>11. Hud</item>
        <item>12. Yusuf</item>
        <item>13. Ar-Ra`d</item>
        <item>14. Ibraheem</item>
        <item>15. Al-Hijr</item>
        <item>16. An-Nahl</item>
        <item>17. Al-Isra</item>
        <item>18. Al-Kahf</item>
        <item>19. Maryam</item>
        <item>20. Ta-Ha</item>
        <item>21. Al-Anbiya</item>
        <item>22. Al-Hajj</item>
        <item>23. Al-Mu`minoon</item>
        <item>24. An-Noor</item>
        <item>25. Al-Furqan</item>
        <item>26. Ash-Shu`ara</item>
        <item>27. An-Naml</item>
        <item>28. Al-Qasas</item>
        <item>29. Al-`Ankabut</item>
        <item>30. Ar-Rum</item>
        <item>31. Luqman</item>
        <item>32. As-Sajdah</item>
        <item>33. Al-Ahzab</item>
        <item>34. Saba</item>
        <item>35. Fatir</item>
        <item>36. Ya seen</item>
        <item>37. As-Saffat</item>
        <item>38. Saad</item>
        <item>39. Az-Zumar</item>
        <item>40. Ghafir</item>
        <item>41. Fussilat</item>
        <item>42. Ash-Shura</item>
        <item>43. Az-Zukhruf</item>
        <item>44. Ad-Dukhan</item>
        <item>45. Al-Jathiyah</item>
        <item>46. Al-Ahqaf</item>
        <item>47. Muhammad</item>
        <item>48. Al-Fath</item>
        <item>49. Al-Hujurat</item>
        <item>50. Qaf</item>
        <item>51. Ad-Dhariyat</item>
        <item>52. At-Tur</item>
        <item>53. An-Najm</item>
        <item>54. Al-Qamar</item>
        <item>55. Ar-Rahman</item>
        <item>56. Al-Waqi`ah</item>
        <item>57. Al-Hadeed</item>
        <item>58. Al-Mujadilah</item>
        <item>59. Al-Hashr</item>
        <item>60. Al-Mumtahina</item>
        <item>61. As-Saff</item>
        <item>62. Al-Jumu`ah</item>
        <item>63. Al-Munafiqun</item>
        <item>64. At-Taghabun</item>
        <item>65. At-Talaq</item>
        <item>66. At-Tahreem</item>
        <item>67. Al-Mulk</item>
        <item>68. Al-Qalam</item>
        <item>69. Al-Haqqah</item>
        <item>70. Al-Ma`aarij</item>
        <item>71. Nuh</item>
        <item>72. Al-Jinn</item>
        <item>73. Al-Muzzammil</item>
        <item>74. Al-Muddathir</item>
        <item>75. Al-Qiyamah</item>
        <item>76. Al-Insan</item>
        <item>77. Al-Mursalat</item>
        <item>78. An-Naba</item>
        <item>79. An-Nazi`at</item>
        <item>80. `Abasa</item>
        <item>81. At-Takweer</item>
        <item>82. Al-Infitar</item>
        <item>83. Al-Mutaffifeen</item>
        <item>84. Al-Inshiqaq</item>
        <item>85. Al-Burooj</item>
        <item>86. At-Tariq</item>
        <item>87. Al-A`la</item>
        <item>88. Al-Ghashiyah</item>
        <item>89. Al-Fajr</item>
        <item>90. Al-Balad</item>
        <item>91. Ash-Shams</item>
        <item>92. Al-Lail</item>
        <item>93. Ad-Dhuha</item>
        <item>94. Al-Inshirah</item>
        <item>95. At-Teen</item>
        <item>96. al-`Alaq</item>
        <item>97. Al-Qadr</item>
        <item>98. Al-Bayyinah</item>
        <item>99. Az-Zalzala</item>
        <item>100. Al-Adiyat</item>
        <item>101. al-Qari`ah</item>
        <item>102. At-Takathur</item>
        <item>103. Al-Asr</item>
        <item>104. Al-Humazah</item>
        <item>105. Al-Feel</item>
        <item>106. Al-Quraish</item>
        <item>107. Al-Maa`oun</item>
        <item>108. Al-Kawthar</item>
        <item>109. Al-Kafiroun</item>
        <item>110. An-Nasr</item>
        <item>111. Al-Masad</item>
        <item>112. Al-Ikhlas</item>
        <item>113. Al-Falaq</item>
        <item>114. An-Nas</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="names_of_Allah">
        <item>99 names of Allah (swt) with meaning, explanations and benefits :
            \n\n\n1. Ar-Rahman ( الرَّحْمَنُ ) :  The Beneficent
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : He who wills goodness and mercy for all His creatures.
                \nBenefits : Who repeat this name 100 times after each fard (Obligatory) prayer will have a good memory, a keen awareness, and be free of a heavy heart.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>2. Ar-Raheem ( الرَّحِيمُ ) : The Merciful
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : He who acts with extreme kindness.
                \nBenefits : Who repeats this name 100 times after each Fajr prayer will find everyone to be friendly towards him and he will be safe from all worldly calamities.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>3. Al-Malik ( الْمَلِكُ ) : The Eternal Lord
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Sovereign Lord, The One with the complete Dominion, the One Whose Dominion is clear from imperfection.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this name many times every day after the Fajr prayer will become rich by the grace of Allah.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>4. Al-Quddus ( الْقُدُّوسُ ) : The Most Sacred
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who is pure from any imperfection and clear from children and adversaries.
                \nBenefits : Agitation never comes close if someone recites it 100 times every day.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>5. As-Salam ( السَّلاَمُ ) : The Embodiment of Peace
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who is free from every imperfection.
                \nBenefits : He, who repeats this name 160 times to a sick person, will help him to regain  He who repeats this name frequently will be safe from all calamities.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>6. Al-Mu`min ( الْمُؤْمِنُ ) : The Infuser of Faith
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who witnessed for Himself that no one is God but Him. And He witnessed for His believers that they are truthful in their belief that no one is God but Him.
                \nBenefits : Who repeats this name 631 times will be safe from harm.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>7. Al-Muhaymin ( الْمُهَيْمِنُ ) : The Preserver of Safety
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who witnesses the saying and deeds of His creatures.
                \nBenefits : He who takes bath and offers two rakats of prayer and repeats this Name 100 times with sincere concentration, Allah will purify his external as well as internal condition.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>8. Al-Aziz ( الْعَزِيزُ ) : The Mighty One
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Strong, The Defeater who is not defeated.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name 41 times after each Fard prayer will be independent of need from others and gain honor after disgrace.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>9. Al-Jabbar ( الْجَبَّارُ ) : The Omnipotent One
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One that nothing happens in His Dominion except that which He willed.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name will not be compelled to do anything against his wishes, and will not be exposed to violence, severity or hardness.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>10. Al-Mutakabbir ( الْمُتَكَبِّرُ ) : The Dominant One
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who is clear from the attributes of the creatures and from resembling them.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name frequently will be granted status and respect. If He repeats this Name frequently at the commencement of every act, He will achieve success by the grace of Allah.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>11. Al-Khaaliq ( الْخَالِقُ ) : The Creator
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who brings everything from non-existence to existence.
                \\nBenefits : Allah will assign an angel to guide the person righteously if he recites this name 100 times continuously for a prescribed limit of 7 days.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>12. Al-Baari ( الْبَارِئُ ) : The Evolver
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Maker, The Creator who has the Power to turn the entities.
                \nBenefits : This name only signifies that Allah created all things in proportion.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>13. Al-Musawwir ( الْمُصَوِّرُ ) : The Flawless Shaper
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who forms His creatures in different pictures.
                \nBenefits : Recite this name 21 times and do a Damm on water. Continue this for 7 consecutive days. Use the water for breaking the fast. Insha’Allah, the women will soon be blessed with a child.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>14. Al-Ghaffaar ( الْغَفَّارُ ) : The Great Forgiver
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Forgiver, The One who forgives the sins of His slaves time and time again.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name will be forgiven his sins.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>15. Al-Qahhaar ( الْقَهَّارُ ) : The All-Prevailing One
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Dominant, The One who has the perfect Power and is not unable over anything.
                \nBenefits: The soul of him who repeats this Name will conquer the desires of the flesh, and his heart will be made free from the attractions of the world and gain inner peace. This Name also frees one from being wronged.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>16. Al-Wahhab ( الْوَهَّابُ ) : The Supreme Bestower.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who is Generous in giving plenty without any return. He is everything that benefits whether Halal or Haram.
                \nBenefits : Reciting it frequently will remove poverty. Reciting it 40 times in the last Sajadah of Chasht prayer will relieve the person from starvation.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>17. Ar-Razzaq ( الرَّزَّاقُ ) : The Total Provider.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Sustainer, The Provider.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name will be provided with sustenance by Allah.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>18. Al-Fattah ( الْفَتَّاحُ ) : The Supreme Solver.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Opener, The Reliever, The Judge, The One who opens for His slaves the closed worldly and religious matters.
                \nBenefits : The heart of him who repeats this Name will be open, and he will be given victory.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>19. Al-Alim ( اَلْعَلِيْمُ ) : The All-Knowing One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Knowledgeable; The One nothing is absent from His knowledge.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name, his heart will become luminous, revealing divine light.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>20. Al-Qaabid ( الْقَابِضُ ) : The Restricting One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Constrictor, The Withholder, The One who constricts the sustenance by His wisdom and expands and widens it with His Generosity and Mercy.
                \nBenefits : He who recite this name on 4 pieces of food (fruit, bread, etc.) and eats them for 40 days will be free from hunger.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>21. Al-Baasit ( الْبَاسِطُ ) : The Extender.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Englarger, The One who constricts the sustenance by His wisdom and expands and widens it with His Generosity and Mercy.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name 10 times after Chasht prayer with open hands (palms up), then rubs his face with his hands, will be free of need from others.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>22. Al-Khaafid ( الْخَافِضُ ) : The Reducer.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Abaser, The One who lowers whoever He willed by His Destruction and raises whoever He willed by His Endowment.
                \nBenefits : Those who fast three days, and on the fourth day repeat this Name 70 times in a gathering, Allah will free them from harm by their enemy. Allah will fulfill the need of one who repeats this Name 500 times daily.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>23. Ar-Rafi ( الرَّافِعُ ) : The Elevating One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Exalter, The Elevator, The One who lowers whoever He willed by His Destruction and raises whoever He willed by His Endowment.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name 101 times day and night, Allah will make him higher, as far as honor, richness, and merit are concerned.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>24. Al-Mu`izz ( الْمُعِزُّ ) : The Honourer-Bestower.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : He gives esteem to whoever He willed, hence there is no one to degrade Him; And He degrades whoever He willed, hence there is no one to give Him esteem.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this name 140 times after Maghrib prayer on Monday or Friday nights, Allah will make him dignified in the eyes of others. That person will fear no one but Allah.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>25. Al-Muzil ( المُذِلُّ ) : The Abaser.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Dishonourer, The Humiliator, He gives esteem to whoever He willed, hence there is no one to degrade Him; And He degrades whoever He willed, hence there is no one to give Him esteem.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name 75 times will be free from harm by those who are jealous of him and wish to harm him. Allah will protect him.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>26. As-Sami ( السَّمِيعُ ) : The All-Hearer.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Hearer, The One who Hears all things that are heard by His Eternal Hearing without an ear, instrument or organ.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name 500, 100 or 50 times without speaking to anyone on Thursday after the chasht prayer, Allah will bestow on him anything he desires.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>27. Al-Baseer ( الْبَصِيرُ ) : The All-Seeing.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The All-Noticing, The One who Sees all things that are seen by His Eternal Seeing without a pupil or any other instrument.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Names 100 times after Friday afternoon prayer, Allah will give this person light in his sight and enlighten his heart.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>28. Al-Hakam ( الْحَكَمُ ) : The Impartial Judge.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Judge, He is the Ruler and His judgment is His Word.
                \nBenefits :He who repeats this Name many times at night, many secrets will be revealed to him.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>29. Al-Adl ( الْعَدْلُ ) : The Embodiment of Justice.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Just, The One who is entitled to do what He does.
                \nBenefits : On Friday night or day, if you write this Name on a piece of bread and eat it, people will obey you.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>30. Al-Lateef ( اللَّطِيفُ ) : The Knower of Subtleties.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Subtle One, The Gracious, The One who is kind to His slaves and endows upon them.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name 133 times daily will have an increase in his sustenance and all his affairs will be settled to his satisfaction.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>31. Al-Khabeer ( الْخَبِيرُ ) : The All-Aware One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who knows the truth of things.
                \nBenefits : If a man is a victim of selfish desires and bad habits he will be relieved of these if he repeats this Name regularly.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>32. Al-Haleem ( الْحَلِيمُ ) : The Clement One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Forebearing, The One who delays the punishment for those who deserve it and then He might forgive them.
                \nBenefits : He, who writes this Name on a piece of paper, washes it with water and sprinkles that water on anything that thing will become safe from loss and calamities.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>33. Al-Azeem ( الْعَظِيمُ ) : The Magnificent One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Great One, The Mighty, The One deserving the attributes of Exaltment, Glory, Extolement, and Purity from all imperfection.
                \nBenefits : Those who repeat this Name many times will be respected.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>34. Al-Ghafoor ( الْغَفُورُ ) : The Great Forgiver.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The All-Forgiving, The Forgiving, The One who forgives a lot.
                \nBenefits : He who has a headache, fever and despondent, and continuously repeats this Name will be relieved of his ailment and will have Allah’s forgiveness.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>35. Ash-Shakoor ( الشَّكُورُ ) : The Acknowledging One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Grateful, The Appreciative, The One who gives a lot of reward for a little obedience.
                \nBenefits : He who is afflicted with monitory troubles or with any other calamity and suffering, if he repeats this Name 41 times daily.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>36. Al-Ali ( الْعَلِيُّ ) : The Sublime One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Most High, The One who is clear from the attributes of the creatures.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name regularly and keep it with him after writing it on a piece of paper will attain high rank, affluence, and success in his (lawful) desires.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>37. Al-Kabeer ( الْكَبِيرُ ) : The Great One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Most Great, The Great, The One who is greater than everything in status.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name 100 times each day will have esteem.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>38. Al-Hafiz ( الْحَفِيظُ ) : The Guarding One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Preserver, The Protector, The One who protects whatever and whoever He willed to protect.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name frequently and keeps it with him will be protected against calamities.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>39. Al-Muqeet ( المُقيِت ) : The Sustaining One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Maintainer, The Guardian, The Feeder, The One who has the Power.
                \nBenefits : If someone with a bad mannered child repeats this Name into a glass of water, and gives this water to the child to drink, the child will have good manners.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>40. Al-Haseeb ( الْحسِيبُ ) : The Reckoning One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Reckoner, The One who gives the satisfaction.
                \nBenefits : He who faces any problem should repeat this Name many times.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>41. Al-Jaleel ( الْجَلِيلُ ) : The Majestic One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Sublime One, The Beneficent, The One who is attributed with greatness of Power and Glory of status.
                \nBenefits : He who writes this Name on a piece of paper with musk and saffron and keeps it with him and repeats this Name frequently will attain honor and status.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>42. Al-Kareem ( الْكَرِيمُ ) : The Bountiful One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Generous One, The Gracious, The One who is attributed with greatness of Power and Glory of status.
                \nBenefits : He who repeats this Name many times at bedtime will have esteem in this world (and the Hereafter among the learned and righteous people).</sub>
        </item>
        <item>43. Ar-Raqeeb ( الرَّقِيبُ ) : The Watchful One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Watcher, The One that nothing is absent from Him. Hence it’s meaning is related to the attribute of Knowledge.
                \nBenefits : Who repeats this Name seven times on himself, his family and property, all will be under Allah’s protection.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>44. Al-Mujeeb ( الْمُجِيبُ ) : The Responding One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Responsive, The Hearkener, The One who answers the one in need if he asks Him and rescues the yearner if he calls upon Him.
                \nBenefits : The appeal of him who repeats this Name will be answered.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>45. Al-Waasi ( الْوَاسِعُ ) : The All-Pervading One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Vast, The All-Embracing, The Knowledgeable.
                \nBenefits : If one who has difficulty in earning, repeats this Name frequently, will have good earnings.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>46. Al-Hakeem ( الْحَكِيمُ ) : The Wise One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Wise, The Judge of Judges, The One who is correct in His doings.
                \n\nBenefits : He who repeats this Name continuously (from time to time) will not have difficulties in his work, and Allah will open to him the door of wisdom.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>47. Al-Wadud ( الْوَدُودُ ) : The Loving One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The One who loves His believing slaves and His believing slaves love Him. His love to His slaves is His Will to be merciful to them and praise them.
                \n\nBenefits : This name helps in resolving a disagreement between two people if one gives the other person food after reciting this name 1000 times in his food.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>48. Al-Majeed ( الْمَجِيدُ ) : The Glorious One.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Most Glorious One, The One who is with perfect Power, High Status, Compassion, Generosity and Kindness.
                \n\nBenefits : He who repeats this Name gains glory.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>49. Al-Ba`ith ( الْبَاعِثُ ) : The Infuser of New Life.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Resurrector, The Raiser (from death), The One who resurrects His slaves after death for reward and/or punishment.
                \n\nBenefits : He who repeats this Name gains the fear of Allah.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>50. Ash-Shaheed ( الشَّهِيدُ ) : The All Observing Witness.
            <sub>\n\nExplanation : The Witness, The One who nothing is absent from Him.
                \n\nBenefits : Recite this name 21 times with the hand placed on the head of the disobedient person. Insha’Allah, he will become obedient.</sub>
        </item>
        <item>51. Al-Haqq</item>
        <item>52. Al-Wakil</item>
        <item>53. Al-Qawi</item>
        <item>54. Al-Matin</item>
        <item>55. Al-Wali</item>
        <item>56. Al-Hamid</item>
        <item>57. Al-Muhsi</item>
        <item>58. Al-Mubdi</item>
        <item>59. Al-Muid</item>
        <item>60. Al-Muhyi</item>
        <item>61. Al-Mumit</item>
        <item>62. Al-Hayy</item>
        <item>63. Al-Qayyum</item>
        <item>64. Al-Wajid</item>
        <item>65. Al-Majid</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
